

### **SKILLS**

- Excellent knowledge of Circana
- Good knowledge of Office Suit, in particular Excel and PowerPoint
- Certification "Digital Marketing fundamentals"
- Certification "Google Analytics advanced"
- Basic knowledge of Photoshop e Premiere Pro

## **LANGUAGES**

- Italian Mother tongue
- German Mother tongue
- English Intermediate
- Spanish B2 In progress



# MARKETING

### JOB PROFILE

Young professional man with strong motivation to learn and grow professionally in the field of Marketing and Trade Marketing with an openness towards sales. During my last work experience I improved the use of the main work tools including Microsoft Excel and Power Point, demonstrating proactivity, excellent communication and interpersonal skills as well as team spirit and the ability to prioritise by organising my work in a rigorous and goal-oriented manner.

### **WORK EXPERIENCES**

### Tech Sales Specialist - Lactalis Italia Spa | 2022-2023

- Point-of-sale activity management and Sell-out agency coordination
- Definition of Sell-out activity KPIs
- Market and competitor analysis
- Analysis of price trends and promotions
- Supporting the Sell-in team in terms of volume and margin results in relation to the product portfolio

# Employee - Ufficio tecnologie e Innovazione Provincia di Bolzano | 2021

- FESR database creation
- Practice Management
- Inspections

# Marketing Intern - Gromia Srl | 2019-2020

- Seo Analysis and Google Analytics
- Newsletter creation
- Social profile management
- Project manager "Recruitment of Milan porters"
- Company website management and updating

### **EDUCATION**

### Cattolica University | 2021-2022

Master in Marketing

### University of Milano Bicocca | 2016-2020

Bachelor's Degree in Marketing, Corporate Communication and Global Markets